If you want to grow,
if you want to grow your brand,
your business, your socials,
maybe one in five videos,
do your own thing. Carte blanche,
as they call it.
But for the other four out of five,
you want to make sure that you
are staying in
line with what's working,
because those channels that
are bigger than you, more
successful than you,
that make more money than you,
when you go and look at what
lead magnet they use
or how they do the introductions to their
videos, you are
actually jumping and skipping past years
of failed attempts and being frustrated
and things that don't work.
Renzo Gracie would've tried so many
submissions that
never worked. John Danaher comes along
and in five years learned what Renzo
learned
in 20 years.
Then Gordon Ryan can come along
and learn in one year what it took
John five years to learn.
It's the exact same on YouTube,
which means that the more
novice you are as a creator coming
through, and the younger you are,
you little
whippersnappers. Even
if you look at the fitness industry,
people that arrive at
training now have so much evidence
and randomized control
trials about hypertrophy, about fat loss.
As time goes on,
you get to skip years of frustration
and not knowing and get
straight to it. So as an early creator,
you have got so much information in front
of you on what works
and what doesn't work,
that life's never been easier.
So 100%, go out there
and look to steal good ideas and
make them better